[Music]
Hello, welcome,
good. My name is Anushmikashi, and in this video,
we will talk about why today the
stock of ICC Lombard is up by 10%.
So, let's start. So, what was happening previously was that as per
RBI regulations and losses,
RBS, asking banks to reduce their take in a
group insurance company, for example,
if there are insurance companies from any group like HDFC Group,
ICC Group, then the
bank's stake in that
insurance company, IBPS, asking banks to
reduce their take. This step was essentially
taken because RBI wanted the
banks to pay
more attention to their banking activities.
So, this was the intention behind
RBI yesterday, but what happened after that was that ICC
Bank, which has 48% stake in ICC Lombard,
ICC Bank had to reduce that by 230% by
September 24, which according to RBI,
they have taken all the approvals etc.
Narmada approved the time extension till
September 2024, but what has happened now is the latest
as you also know.  It is said that the
approval received by HDFC Bank is to increase its stock in
HDFC Life by more than 50%. Similarly,
ICC Bank also discussed
this in its board meeting and they have unloaded their stock in the said debt. They want to
increase the
stock from 48% to more than 50%. They will increase the stock by an additional 4%
in their ICC Lombard.
So, primarily because of
this action, where there was an overhang earlier
and reducing the stock, right now that overhang has turned into
increasing stock. Now,
because of such things, the stock of ICC Lombard
today is approximately 8 to 10% * debt
trading session. So, but of this bank,
they have decided this in the board meeting. But
this thinks it is
subject to regulatory approvals, so we should keep this
thing in mind. So, this was it. I hope
you liked this video. Stay tuned
to our channel for more such videos.
Thank you so much.
[music]